{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Masterson",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Masterson, Peter",
    "human_readable": "The name of Peter Masterson is Masterson, Peter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9742283821105957,
            "question": "What is the given name of Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9585815072059631,
            "question": "What is Peter Masterson's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.950529932975769,
            "question": "Is 'Masterson' the first or last name of Peter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9022127389907837,
            "question": "What is the family name of Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.743412435054779,
            "question": "What information does this statement provide about Peter Masterson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7178102135658264,
            "question": "How would you write Peter Masterson's name in reverse order?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.694996178150177,
            "question": "What is the relationship between 'Masterson' and 'Peter' in this context?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5697505474090576,
            "question": "If someone introduced Peter as 'Peter', would they be using his full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4388086199760437,
            "question": "Could you use only one of the names to refer to Peter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03786441683769226,
            "question": "Is there a specific order for writing someone's name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Peter Masterson is Masterson, Peter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6411_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you use only one of the names to refer to Peter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6411_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone introduced Peter as 'Peter', would they be using his full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6411_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between 'Masterson' and 'Peter' in this context?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6411_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6411_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to the individual as \"Peter Masterson,\" confirming that his full name is indeed \"Masterson, Peter.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}